<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Musings of an engineer...</title>
    <link>https://xanderguzman.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Musings of an engineer...</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© 2020 Xander Guzman</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 14:22:15 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://xanderguzman.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chatterbox a gRPC Project</title>
      <link>https://xanderguzman.com/post/chatterbox-a-grpc-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 14:22:15 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xanderguzman.com/post/chatterbox-a-grpc-project/</guid>
      <description>I was recently thinking about starting a gRPC project just to kick the tires and get a feel for how the technology worked. In the past I&amp;rsquo;ve only played with it for a short while and this was during the proto2 days. To give this a go I spent a couple of days learning about the proto3 specification and then trying to think of something worth spending the time and effort on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Greetings</title>
      <link>https://xanderguzman.com/post/greetings/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 13:16:01 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xanderguzman.com/post/greetings/</guid>
      <description>Yay another website Yep it&amp;rsquo;s that time again, that time where I have the spare time to look at my personal website and make a decision about what I want it to be about and what content I want to live on it. I think this is a good start.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://xanderguzman.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xanderguzman.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Greetings and Salutations This website is a place to collect my random musings and thoughts. I&amp;rsquo;ve been a professional software engineer since 2006 and have a breadth of experience in many industries. I pride myself on writing software in a clean and maintainable way. I&amp;rsquo;m not that big of a blogger so you may not find too many updates to the website but when I feel like it I&amp;rsquo;ll post things about my interests.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://xanderguzman.com/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xanderguzman.com/projects/</guid>
      <description>Software Engineering  HiveD :: A small game engine built around the Hive board game.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xander Guzman</title>
      <link>https://xanderguzman.com/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xanderguzman.com/resume/</guid>
      <description>xander.guzman@xanderguzman.com Denver, CO USA   Technical Experience  Amazon Web Services (AWS) AWS Lambda, Step Functions, API Gateway (V1), KMS, STS, IAM, CloudFormation, CodePipeline, CodeBuild, CodeCommit, Kinesis, Kinesis Firehose, Cognito, Athena, AWS Glue Programming Languages Go (1.x), Python (2.x), Python (3.x), PHP, C#, Java, C++ (C++11/C++98), C (C99) Data Stores RDS, Aurora, DynamoDB, S3, ElasticCache, Elastic Search, SNS, SQS, PostgreSQL, mySQL Containers Docker, Docker Compose, EC2, ECS, Fargate Operating Systems MacOS, Ubuntu 12.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
